get-music.net 2007-12-11

# Privacy Policy @ Get-Music.net

Privacy Policy 

Your privacy is important to us. Get-Music.net service is free for all to use, and prior registration is not needed for use of Get-Music.net service.

Get-Music.net will explicitly ask when it needs information that personally identifies you. All the personally identifiable information we collect are only gathered with your voluntary act. Get-Music.net keeps all the personal information private and does not, and will not, share it with any third parties except under these circumstances.

  * When such action is necessary to conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process
  * When such action is necessary to protect and defend rights or property of Get-Music.net
  * When such action is necessary to enforce Get-Music.net terms of service

Get-Music.net may use cookies to enhance your surfing experience, but cookies will not be used under any circumstances to personally identify you without your prior consent.

Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by AdReactor, our advertising network. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site.   
For more information about AdReactor, please visit [their website](http://www.adreactor.com/ "Adreactor.com").

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

If you think Get-Music.net has violated any of these privacy policies, please contact us immediately. 

13:11:48 - crazyken2007 (Hong Kong)  
13:08:56 - amr_hmd (Egypt)  
13:08:50 - kalel29 (Algeria)  
13:08:08 - sabuju (Namibia)  
13:07:50 - natalia.mi (Slovakia (slovak Republic))  
12:58:50 - kunyuksira (Indonesia)  
12:57:54 - tadpad (Thailand)  
12:57:11 - lothiras (Serbia And Montenegro)
